enc.com.pk 2012-03-19

# Privacy Statement & Complaint Process | ENC

**ENC’s Privacy Policy**  
ENC respects the privacy of all parties with whom we deal. ENC adheres to the principles contained in Data Protection Act 1998.

Collection of personal information:ENC collects students’ personal information insofar as it is necessary for processing applications and otherwise efficiently performing services sought by students. Information typically collected would include; name, address, contact details, educational background, family contacts, credit card details and Visa details. ENC does not collect superfluous personal information in order to create a database for any other party’s use.

Use of personal information: ENC will normally only use your personal information in connection with the service you require. In most cases, this will be in connection with applications to educational institutions and for visa applications. Some of the information could be used in ENC promotional materials. ENC may at times be required by law to supply your personal information to the relevant authorities.

**Consent:**  
Wherever required by law to obtain your consent before supplying your personal information, ENC will seek your consent.

**Complaints Process**  
ENC is committed to dealing with complaints in accordance with the rules of natural justice. Implicit in this is the necessity for the following:

• The complainant is to be allowed the opportunity to be heard in a manner which provides sufficient time and information for the complainant to prepare a statement.  
• The person considering the complaint should do so with an open mind and without bias.  
• The complaint is to be dealt with promptly.  
• Any decision is to be conveyed to the complainant in writing.

**Complaints Procedure**  
If a student has a complaint, whether against ENC or a higher education provider, he/she should email their complaints to complaints@enc.com.pk

**Responding To Your Complaint**  
After you have lodged your complaint, we will answer you in writing within fourteen (14) days. If you are not satisfied with the response, you can request that the matter be referred to Shikoh Lashari, CEO, who will provide a written reply within a further fourteen (14) days.
